fabbeautydress.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

FabBeautyDress.com collects customer information to improve your overall website navigation experience with us.We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining and using this information responsibly.

Information Collection and Use

FabBeautyDress.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.We will not sell,share, rent or exchange this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.All information gathered by FabBeautyDress.com through your visit,is kept strictly confidential and will not be distributed to any company or individual.Ever.Any personal information you provide to us on our website when you sign our mailing list,or request information(i.e.name, address,e-mail address,telephone number)is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems.FabBeautyDress.com will not sell,rent nor share your email address with others for them to send you unsolicited email.

Receiving email promotions

If you give us your email address when you register,we will send you emails about promotions.To remove yourself from our mailing list,simply click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message.

About "cookies"

Although FabBeautyDress.com will use "cookies" to track user patterns on its web site,FabBeautyDress.com will not use cookies to learn the identity of its users,nor attempt to track users after they leave the FabBeautyDress.com site. Futher,cookies will not be used by FabBeautyDress.com to gather specific personal information about individual,and FabBeautyDress.com will not participate in any external site tracking programs.Nor will we share any cookie-generated information about individual users or user patterns.

Aout Demograhpic

FabBeautyDress.com will compile site-wide demographic information that it will not compile profiles of individual users,including the gathering of names,addresses,email addresses and other personal information.

User IP

FabBeautyDress.com tracks user IP addresses for the purposes of systems administraion,demographic profiling and traffic logging,but FabBeautyDress.com will not use IP addresses to try to identify individual users of FabBeautyDress.com

Policy Changes and Questions

FabBeautyDress.com may update our privacy policy from time to time and use of the information we collect now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use.Whenever we make a change,we will post the updated policy at this site and we encourage you to check our policy periodically.By using our website following the posting of a change in the privacy policy,you consent to the updated policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy,please contact us.

Choice and Opt-Out

If you no longer wish to receive the Company's promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing the Company at service@fabbeautydress.com.
